<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Code Blog</title>
    <description>Personal blog page where you get to see all my projects</description>
    <link>http://mnive93.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://mnive93.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Chrome App Development!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So now for my first side project I am planning to develop a Chrome app which will help me dig deeper into Javascript (which I am very very weak at)! The idea of my Chrome app is something similar to that of LinkedIn Pulse app but with a twist ! You get to subscribe to many channels or even add a channel that you wish to receive updates. By channels I mean their RSS feed. So the twist is that I am planning to let you filter your news with a set of keywords which will help you stay updated in the news that you are interested in. So this is raw basic idea of my chrome app.It requires a bit of tweaking. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Obstacles &lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I might be facing is to process the RSS feed of the channel.Not every channels have well        maintained RSS feed.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Filtering the content . So in order to filter the content I might have to scrape the content of the webpage.In order to scrape the content I am planning to use a JS library to do the trick. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Node.js offers a good scraping library so the next obstacle is integrating Node.js with Chrome Apps.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I have listed down all the issues that I will be tackling . It’s challenging , but hey I am doing this only for the challenge. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://mnive93.github.io/tech/2014/08/22/Chrome%20App%20Development/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnive93.github.io/tech/2014/08/22/Chrome%20App%20Development/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello World!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is going to be my personal blogpage which is created using Jekyll . I have never seen such clean and crisp structure.I have fallen in love with the beautiful and simple UI.Okay now let’s get into business.I am going to start blogging and make use of my ample free time productively.I am planning to work on various side projects and this is where you get to see how they are done. So let’s get started!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Perfection is achieved, not when there is nothing more to add, but when there is nothing left to take away.
  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://mnive93.github.io/jekyll/2014/08/11/my-very-first-post/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnive93.github.io/jekyll/2014/08/11/my-very-first-post/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
