<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Code Blog</title>
    <description>Personal blog page where you get to see all my projects</description>
    <link>http://mnive93.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://mnive93.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Purpose Of Life</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever felt so depressed for no reason at all? You just get up one fine morning and it doesn’t feel quite right.Something is missing. Why is that sometimes life feels so empty? Like you are closed inside a cage and you are not able to break free.I ask my mom and she says you got the best things in life so just stop whining!When you have carved a path for yourself.You try traversing those roads but suddenly you are thrown away far from your route for no reason at all . Now you have no clue which route to take to come back on track. I am here all alone in unknown roads with a heavy baggage having no clue where I am supposed to go in life!Should I be satisfied and content with what I have right now ? Or am I being so greedy asking for more from life?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I console myself with the cliche “Maybe something better is waiting for me”.Yeah I know that is just pure bullshit but that is the only thing which is keeping me on the other side of insanity.I must never give up on my dreams afterall that’s the only luxury I have right now , “my dreams”! They are my own and no one can snatch them away from me . &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is the ultimate purpose of our lives ? Just preserve our species? So many questions pounding inside my head but I fail to answer them EVERY.SINGLE.TIME.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&quot;If winter comes can Spring be far behind ? Have some hope . &quot;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://mnive93.github.io/life/2014/08/27/Purpose-Of-Life/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnive93.github.io/life/2014/08/27/Purpose-Of-Life/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chrome App Development</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So now for my first side project I am planning to develop a Chrome app which will help me dig deeper into Javascript (which I am very very weak at)! The idea of my Chrome app is something similar to that of LinkedIn Pulse app but with a twist ! You get to subscribe to many channels or even add a channel that you wish to receive updates. By channels I mean their RSS feed. So the twist is that I am planning to let you filter your news with a set of keywords which will help you stay updated in the news that you are interested in. So this is raw basic idea of my chrome app.It requires a bit of tweaking. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Obstacles &lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I might be facing a problem to process the RSS feed of the channel.Not every channels have well     maintained RSS feed.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Filtering the content . So in order to filter the content I might have to scrape the content of the webpage.In order to scrape the content I am planning to use a JS library to do the trick. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Node.js offers a good scraping library so the next obstacle is integrating Node.js with Chrome Apps.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I have listed down all the issues that I will be tackling . It’s challenging , but hey I am doing this only for the challenge. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
“It does not matter how slowly you go so long as you do not stop.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://mnive93.github.io/tech/2014/08/22/Chrome-App-Development/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnive93.github.io/tech/2014/08/22/Chrome-App-Development/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello World</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is going to be my personal blogpage which is created using Jekyll . I have never seen such clean and crisp structure.I have fallen in love with the beautiful and simple UI.Okay now let’s get into business.I am going to start blogging and make use of my ample free time productively.I am planning to work on various side projects and this is where you get to see how they are done. So let’s get started!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Perfection is achieved, not when there is nothing more to add, but when there is nothing left to take away.
  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://mnive93.github.io/jekyll/2014/08/11/Hello-World/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnive93.github.io/jekyll/2014/08/11/Hello-World/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
